## Christian Colewan

### WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a web developer with knowledge of Laravel and Vue.js, as well as Vuetify, Bootstrap, and Material Design for the front end. I can create web designs using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. I have background in database management using MySQL and PGSQL. I have also experienced deploying websites using online hosting sites such as Hostinger, Netlify and GoDaddy. I have used GitHub, Bitbucket for my repositories. I have also some knowledge in Git for the version control of my projects. As for my projects, I have created inventory systems, an e-commerce mobile app, and management systems.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Full-Stack ProficiencyStrategic Database Management UI/UX Mastery Version Control and Collaboration Solution Diversity Deployment Expertise Problem Solving Communication Adaptability

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Sahei Core Technologies Web Developer

May 2023 - Present

- Voting System Deployment in Kalinga. Took 3 days each trip and we went there for 3 trips
- · Created Student Management Suite
- Created a Pharmacy POS. It has a dental clinic, a remittance center and a grocery store.
- Created an ecommerce mobile application/website for Benguet Farmers.

Freelance Web Developer Dec 2023 - Feb 2023

Created a accident prediction system using database from MMDA

## **EDUCATION**

### **Benguet State University**

Aug 2018 - May 2023

**Bachelor of Science in Information Technology** 

· Thesis - Payroll Management System

### **Data Center College of the Philippines**

Information Communication Technology

Aug 2016 - May 2018

Mil-an National Highschool

Electrical Installation and Maintenance Jun 2012 - April 2016

## PERSONAL DETAIL

Full Name: Christian Fiarawe Colewan

Age: 23 years old

**Date of Birth:** February 13, 2000 **Email:** cts.colewan@gmail.com

Address: 23 Kadaclan Village, Baguio City, Benguet

LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/christian-colewan-a936b713a/

**Contact Number:** +63-995-713-9671 **Portfolio:** christiancolewan.netlify.app/